

THITTAWAN WONGLOR

A highly motivated individual with strong skills in Network, Web Development, UX/UI Design and Embedded Systems. During my internship with a government agency, I developed an asset management system using React, Bootstrap, Laravel, and Oracle Database. Moreover, my experience as a student leader has honed my teamwork, problem-solving, and leadership abilities, which I bring to every project. Which mean I'm committed to continuous learning and delivering high-impact contributions to your organization.

MY CONTACTS



20 February 2002 (Age 22)



096-304-5365



thittawan.wo@gmail.com



73 Soi Seansuk, Prachasongkhro Rd. Din Daeng Sub-district, Din Daeng District, Bangkok. 10400

SOFT SKILLS

- Leadership
- Teamwork
- Communication
- · Design Thinking
- Critical Thinking & Problem Solving

HARD SKILLS

- Programming Languages
 - 。 C
- Javascript
- o C++
- HTML
- Python
- CSS
- Java
- SQL
- PHP
- Web Development
- UX/UI Design
- Network
- Embedded Systems



SCAN ME FOR MORE INFORMATION

EDUCATION

July 2020 - November 2024

• Bachelor of Engineering Computer Engineering and Informatics (GPA 2.79)

EXPERIENCES

April 2021 - March 2022

• Student Council of Kasetsart University Sriracha Campus Chairman of the Corporate Image and Communications Committee

April 2022 - March 2023

Faculty of Engineering at Sriracha Student Union
 President of Faculty of Engineering at Sriracha Student Union

September 2022

• TESA TOP GUN Rally #16 (Device Development for Metaverse)

Overall Score TOP 10 (Gold Medal)

April 2023 - March 2024

• Student Council of Kasetsart University Sriracha Campus Chairman of the Internal Affairs and Property Committee

June 2024 - October 2024

• Department of Science Service (DSS) Full Stack Developer (Co-operative Education)

PROJECTS

Exploratory Project in Computing

• Embedded Systems
KUSRC Smart Farm Project.

Software Engineering

Web Development
 EVILA - EV Online Store Website Project.

Co-operative Education

Full Stack Developer
 DSS Inventory Management System Website Project.
 Laravel 11 (Backend) and Vite+React (Frontend)